[Applause]
[Music]
so this is the letter signed by over a
thousand public health officials arguing
that while COBIT 19 kills racism
predates Govan 19 and kills more and
therefore protesting is a legitimate
response to to the current situation
despite the fact that lock downs are in
place and still are you know basically
as up now so one of the one of the
things in this letter I'll just
highlight it and I can't highlight it
it's right when my cursor is here there
it is
oppose any use of tear gas smoke or
other respiratory irritants which could
increase risk for kovat 19 by making the
respiratory tract more susceptible to
infection exacerbating existing
inflammation and inducing coughing so
that's that's all I wanted to say there
Zack that sounds at one level like these
public health officials are trying to
temper their frankly ludicrous assertion
that it's a legitimate move to go out on
mass under the streets because this is a
bigger because the killing of the the
senseless and violent killing of one man
at the hands of a bad police officer is
more of a public health threat than coab
in nineteen that's that's a ridiculous
statement right now but in this they say
well but you know you don't want to
inflame your lungs sounds right and yet
one thing that you reported that this
homeland security officer told you
yesterday really puts this into stark
relief I think which is he said we're
having our tools taken away from us
we're having our are low impact tools
like like like smoke and even teargas
taken away and a virgin that leaves us
with more and more lethal tools yeah
yeah so I should probably say a little
bit more and I really I hope I this was
not sent to me in confidence I obviously
wanted to talk to me for a reason that
had everything to do with my public
facing life I guess so I'm assuming that
I'm at liberty to talk about this but he
said a number of things one is he said
they're not going to cede the federal
buildings they can't it's their mandate
not to and the federal officers yeah and
that
are fully capable of protecting those
buildings what they're not fully capable
of doing is protecting those buildings
and keeping the rioters safe they cannot
simultaneously do that so the point is
the rioters have a tool which is they
can force these federal officers into
lethal violence which will of course
what do you imagine would happen at this
moment in the Georgia flawed protests
when lethal violence is brought on
protest protesters by federal officers
right this is potentially shot heard
around the world stuff and in my opinion
the anarchists are actually looking for
a massacre and let me explain to you
what I mean by that because obviously
the idea that anybody would seek to be
massacred is ludicrous and it is
ludicrous but you have how many major
cities engaged in violent conflict on a
daily basis now if one of those cities
sees a massacre it does the job that the
anarchists would like right it will be
used to illustrate the illegitimacy and
the overreaction of of the government
and so if you have all of these
anarchists in all of these cities the
chances that you will be in the city
where the massacre happens are low so
provoke provoke provoke and probably it
doesn't happen where you are but it'll
happen somewhere and that's good enough
and even if you're in the city where it
happens chances that you are among the
massacred pretty low so there's a game
being played I believe in which the idea
is to precipitate violence that will be
used to justify what comes next
and the point is just as we all take a
risk when we get behind the wheel of our
car thinking it's very unlikely to be me
that gets killed there's an advantage to
driving so I'm going to accept that risk
the anarchists are accepting that risk
of a small risk of being massacred in
order to precipitate a massacre
somewhere which will do their bidding
now the problem is
that the anarchists are undercutting the
legitimacy of the actual protests that
started this
they've thoroughly undercut it already
and they are co-opting this movement for
what I regard is a completely insane
objective they actually believe that if
you tore civilization down what would
replace it would be better now a we
might not survive it's being torn down
and B the chances that what replaces it
is better are very near zero it's just
like it's like the argument that we
should terraform Mars because the
environment on the earth is lousy well
the environment on the earth is getting
worse it's always gonna be harder to
terraform Mars is you know is America a
fair place I don't think it's fair
enough I think we have real problems but
the chances that tearing it down is
gonna create a fair replacement no it's
gonna create a power vacuum and what's
gonna happen in a power vacuum is the
powerful are gonna rise you're gonna
make things far worse so the anarchists
don't have the right to push us into
this madness what they do potentially
have is the power and why do they have
the power they have the power because
somehow we have been led to accept a
world in which those who would lead are
doing something that sort of sounds like
leadership but it doesn't have the power
people can click away from from their
would-be leaders on the internet where
they follow their leaders to useful
effect in many cases historically
speaking so how the heck are we gonna
bail ourselves out of the situation so a
small really tiny number of anarchists
don't lead the rest of us into a
conflagration that all will end up
regretting
[Music]